No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Faster!
We must arrive at Bilecik Castle at once!
Guards!
Look sharp!
Alps!
They'll be here soon.
We will uprise!
Now it is time to massacre!
We are going to appropriate all the goods!
No enemy shall remain alive!
As you command, my Bey!
Go!
Defend!
Protect the caravan!
God is with us!
Allahu Aqbar
(Allah is the greatest)
Feodor!
If God is with you...
...why are you running like a jackal
running away from a lion?
Confront me!
Come on!
Hurry!
Hurry up, brothers!
I have been stabbed on my shoulder
so many times that...
I don't feel it anymore, Osman.
Your head... You will feel it when
I cut your head.
Three days ago.
Bilecik Castle
Priest Gregor and his friend Andreas
are not in their rooms.
So, where are they, Feodor?
It seems they left willingly.
What do you think?
Do you agree with your commander?
Yes sir.
Take him out!
Now!
You stay, Feodor!
It was really weird that Osman gave up on
Gregor without any resistance.
Now I get it, he set up a game.
So, what about Gregor?
Why did he go back to Osman with
his own will?
I don't know, sir.
Do not interrupt me while I am
thinking out loud, Feodor!
You should have already learned that!
Dear Gregor...
...let's see what is the reason that
you went back to Osman.
Hey Passanger!
Where is your destination?
Kizil Elma.
Osman Bey.
The Priest...
The Priest run away with something
more precious than himself!
You own the most precious
sacred of the Christian world.
What does make it so precious?
What you are holding in your hand
may cause a new Crusades.
A piece of the shroud
that Jesus was crucified.
They believe that Jesus' blood dripped
on this shroud.
This news is all over Constantinople.
The Emperor got mad.
This news was delivered to all the lords.
They will unite and attack you Osman Bey.
You should be careful, Osman Bey.
They may attack anytime.
What a beautiful justice!
Osman Bey holds their most precious...
And they would call me devil.
You say all the Christians unite against
me for this.
What if I make my move first and gain the
support of Christian community?
This would be a very dangerous move,
Osman Bey.
Only the brave can manage difficulty.
You are my eyes and ears.
If you have new news, let me know.
As you command, Osman Bey.
Now it's my time to set up a game.
Harmankaya Castle.
Rogatus knows what he is doing.
He took Turgut from me by using
Catalans.
He took him from me and gave him to Osman.
In return of what?
In return of Priest Gregor.
My predicts are always true!
Where was that Priest we were
looking for?
In Osman's hands.
I told you.
Kosses.
You didn't know that, did you?
Because if you knew, it'd be inevitable
that you'd use Turgut with Rogatus.
You wouldn't hide such a swap from me.
Am I right?
We are on the same side, Nicola.
Why would I hide something like this?
Caesar and Brutus.
They were on the same side too, Kosses.
That you suspect us is heartbreaking,
dear Nicola.
Our only aim was to put your gift
in his place.
Besides, Rogatus gave Turgut, whom you fight
to capture, to Osman, your biggest enemy.
All the self sacrifice you committed for
me has been wasted.
What Rogatus did
cannot remain unpenalized.
The penalty will be heavy.
I'll leave him a scar
that he won't forget.
You say it may cause Crusades, Osman Bey!
Can we take that?
We must take that risk so that our
children don't experience the same, brother.
Their aim is neither the Priest
nor the shroud.
All they want is to banish us.
They want to prevent us from
having our homeland here.
My Sheik father would say
"every situation is under Lord's control"
If Christians are able to attack, we are
able to dispel.
Eyvallah (of course)
Faith comes first, my Bey.
We have religious warriors
to fight off their army.
Thank Allah, we have.
My intention is...
that we may conquer the castles, the towns
from inside...
with the help of the Priest Gregor.
We are going to obtain the support of
non-Muslims.
We will do that with the help of
Priest Gregor.
Those Lords will come here!
They will knee!
They will beg!
They will see that...
Their heart is in our hand.
We are going to rip it out when we want!
My Bey, we should start gaining their
support then.
Let the Priest arrive in Sogut.
He must have just got out.
He'll try again.
That's what we want, Malhun.
My Bey, we are going to Sogut
with Malhun Hatun for the rugs.
Eyvallah.
Eyvallah(okay) Hatuns.
Bilecik Castle.
Does he not trust me at all?
There is only one way to learn it all.
What was that old man's name?
- The one in the church in Sogut.
- Yun.
Hah, Yun.
Find Yun, tell him to learn the truth from
Gregor.
Stop. Wait.
There's one more thing.
Inform the Lords in Bithynia. I will be waiting
for them tomorrow, in my castle.
Kosses included.
As you command.
Harmankaya Castle.
Are you alright?
Will you help me stand up, brother?
Of course.
Did I hurt you?
You should not have
underestimated me, brother.
You are right. No Palailogos
should be underestimated.
My lord.
There is important news
from Bilecik.
Speak.
Lord Rogatus invites all lords
for tomorrow.
He took Priest Gregor.
He will demonstrate his
power to all of us.
He can't, my lord.
The other news is about this.
Everyone is talking about how Gregor
escaped Bilecik to return Osman.
To Osman?
By his own will?
Now, I'm interested in his invitation.
What should we do?
We'll go and see what he
has to say.
But firstly...
I need to see Osman.
Will you ask for Gregor, brother?
Of course.
But this time, I'll let him know
that it's the emperor's wish.
Osman will still refuse.
I know this, Mari.
But his time, he won't
be facing Lord Rogatus.
It's Michael Kosses with the
support of the Byzantine Emperor.
It's time that Osman realizes this.
Come on, alps!
We need to return before the sun fall!
Bala? Won't you talk to me?
The arrogance you showed to Gökçe
hurt the whole tribe.
Wouldn't you be mad?
If you are showing weakness,
who should I trust?
You are right, Bala.
I made a mistake.
Forgive me.
Can I shoot, Osman Bey?
Here, Kosses.
Bala.
Will you stay resentful?
Can one stay resentful to her sister?
Bala.
You'll be in my hands soon.
Alps! Watch out!
Bala, be careful!
We'll kick Osman out of these
lands!
You vile dog!
My child!
Bala! Bala!
-Bala!
-We are retreating!
-My child...
Bala!
You are a strong woman.
Hang on!
My child...
Bala, stay strong!
We are returning to the tribe!
Come on!
Bala! Bala!
Using a Turkish bow takes skill.
After all...
the bow is short,
the arrow is short...
the draw is short.
You seem to carry that skill, Osman Bey.
You didn't come here to watch
archery drill, Kosses.
You know well why I'm here.
Priest Gregor.
Holding someone that the emperor
wants this much...
is a brave act.
But when is it seen that bravery
stops destruction?
If you insist...
the emperor will be so mad.
There will be heavy retaliations.
The news spread as fast as my arrows.
I didn't expect you this soon.
Bhytinia is a small place.
So, what's your offer, Kosses?
Should we give you the priest and
relieve from all burden?
Yes, that's exactly what I'm offering,
Osman Bey.
It's in your hands to end it before
it's getting any worse.
If you continue like this, I'm afraid
the emperor...
We've been living with you in these
lands for a long time.
I thought you knew about the Turks.
Priest Gregor took refuge in us.
Not you, even if the emperor
himself comes here...
he can't take someone who took
refuge in us.
Tell this to the emperor.
-Allah is immortal!
-Allah is just!
My bey, who's sword is this?
Who would it be, master?
My son Orhan!
Mashallah!
Allah is immortal!
Allah is just!
Alaca?
Alaca!
Stay calm.
Tell me what happened.
What happened?
Mother Selcan!
Bala!
Bala! Bala!
Speak! What is this?
What happened?
Who did this?
Tell me!
Who?
She was hit on her belly.
What are you saying?
Osman!
My child...
My baby...
Bala!
Move out of my way!
Osman!
Mother!
To the tent! Come on!
Hurry!
Bala, hang on.
Move out!
Come on, mother.
Hang on, Bala.
Hang on!
Mother!
Bala!
-Bala!
-Move out!
My pretty daughter...
Stay strong.
Bala.
Mother...
-Speak, mother.
-Her wound is light, son.
-Thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
The baby?
The baby, mother?
-You get out.
-Mother?
-Get out, Osman!
-Don't go!
What if our baby dies...
Don't leave, Osman.
I'm here. Don't worry, I'm here.
Come on, my lion.
Come on.
My pretty girl.
Bring water, come on!
Mother, my child!
My child!
Mother!
You will stay strong, my child.
Your child will be alright and
so will you.
Who did this, Malhun?
Catalonians, my bey.
We were returning from Söğüt.
They set an ambush.
We've beaten them, of course.
But...
''We'll banish Osman from
these lands.''
they say.
-Göktuğ.
-My bey.
Gather the alps.
Destroy them!
Create a blood pool!
All the rivers will flow red today!
They will, my bey.
Göktuğ!
Don't let me down!
Bring me his corpse!
As you order, my bey.
Come on, brothers!
My Allah.
Don't give us the loss of a child.
Don't put Bala in despair.
Osman!
Bilecik Castle
Come, Theodor.
Have you found him?
I have, my lord.
I told him what you said.
So, what did he say?
Priest Gregor is my close friend
as much as he is Rogatus'.
He said that he'll do as you want
and learn the truth.
Good. Good.
Good.
Battle without Cerkutay is
too silent.
That mad man.
Where is Cerkutay and Aygül?
My bey must've given them a task.
I don't know.
Catalonians take this road
to their denn.
We won't let them.
We'll strike them.
Be ready.
They might be here any moment.
Let's not let our bey down.
Let's do this as we need to.
We'll kill those dogs, inshallah.
Alright.
They are coming, my bey.
They aren't many.
Come on!
To your positions!
Where are they?
An ambush!
Come on! Come on, Göktuğ!
Allah Allah!
Stand closer, alps!
Stand closer!
Stop!
Isn't Osman Bey here?
I thought he would come personally.
My bey isn't required to kill you.
Wait.
Come on!
This isn't good. Come with Osman Bey
next time.
We will return, Anselmo!
We will return!
Osman!
Bala!
-Bala!
-Thank Allah.
Are you alright?
Our child...
Mother, is my baby alright?
Is my child healthy, mother?
-Mother?
-You are both healthy, thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
Mother...
This is a miracle.
Mashallah.
-Bala.
-Mother.
Thank Allah, son.
Thank Allah.
I was so afraid, Osman.
I was so afraid to lose him.
Bala.
I was in many battles...
I've overcome many calamities...
but today...
I was never as afraid as
I was today.
I was so afraid to lose you.
That something could happen to you...
I was so afraid that something could
happen to our baby.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah
I brought soup, my bey.
Malhun.
Come, come.
Slowly, slowly.
Slowly.
With the name of Allah.
May it heal you.
Harmankaya Castle
Tell me, Bahadır.
How is our priest?
They have been protecting him
better than ever.
They even examine the food.
We already know that.
However, they can't stop someone brave
like you...
with these precautions.
You will kill that Priest...
Bahadır.
I do all these just to
live, Kosses.
If I die at the end
of it, what's the point?
Of course.
Thanks for the offer...
Sir Kosses.
You can't get out of here alive, Bahadır.
However, if you try to
kill Priest Gregor...
you may have a chance to live.
If you change your mind when
you get out of here...
just know that you are not protected as
much as Priest Gregor.
I will do everything I can.
That's what I thought.
You can leave.
Do you think he will succeed?
- If you want, the Emperor can help...
- No!
No!
The Emperor already knows everything.
I already feel humiliated because I can
not take Priest back.
I can't let that happen again.
Bahadır will kill the Priest.
I will serve his dead body to the Emperor.
That's it.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
I can't look at your face, my Bey.
I don't deserve to be your Alp.
You can punish me, my Bey.
I deserve what you will do to me.
You couldn't punish those dogs who
tried to kill...
my Hatun...
and other Hatuns in the tent.
I told you to kill them!
You couldn't!
You couldn't kill them!
You had so many horses but you couldn't
ride onto them!
You didn't take revenge of my Hatun.
You disappointed me.
Get out of here!
The castle is well protected, my Bey.
Nikola is a coward. Of course he
is cautious.
Yes he is.
However, he will get out of there.
Then we will catch him.
I want to know his every step.
Your command, my Bey.
He is being watched in the castle.
Thank you.
I won't feel comfortable ever...
before I punish those dogs.
First Nikola, then Rogatus...
and Kosses! They will pay for
what they have done.
And Catalans.
I have news.
Göktuğ, the Alp of Osman Bey, attacked
Catalans.
- Did they succeed?
- No, my Bey.
If Osman Bey didn't succeed in this, we
should beat Catalans.
Follow these ignobles.
We will take revenge on them too.
Your command, my Bey.
My Bala.
Drink this. May it be good for you.
Bismillâhirrahmânirrahîm. (in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Mashallah.
Can I come in?
Come in, my Sheikh.
Come in.
My daughter.
Please feel comfortable.
My Sheikh, welcome.
I was afraid, my Sheikh.
Thank Allah...
Bismillâhirrahmânirrahîm. (in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Your mother wrapped you with this.
You will wrap your child with this.
Thank Allah that you and my
grandchild is healthy.
Bad things happen.
Your sadness will make you forgiven in the
afterlife.
Amin
Amin, my Sheikh.
While one of you is under the sun, another
can't sit under the cloud.
When Hadrat Hatice...
felt love towards Hadrat Muhammad...
she did everything.
When a woman loved a man...
it was seen as a sin.
Our Hadrat Hatice's love
for our Prophet...
was so big that she didn't care...
about what people said and she wanted
to marry.
Our Prophet felt the same and...
he and our mother Hadrat Hatice...
married.
While everyone was against Muhammad
Mustafa, whose name is a beauty...
"may the blessings of Allah be upon him!"
our mother Hadrat Hatice...
always protected and...
sided with our Prophet.
Our mother Hatice was so in love with our
Prophet that...
while our Prophet made his way to tell
about Islan to other people...
our mother Hatice waited under the sun...
as she didn't want to wait under the clouds...
while he was under the sun.
She waited under the sun.
Thanks to her.
The love between
Hadrat Hatice and Our Prophet...
affected you the same.
May Allah make it forever.
- Amin.
- Amin, my Sheikh.
Brother.
My brother.
I wish he was mad at me.
I wish he hit me.
So that I would feel myself.
I couldn't be worthy of him.
Göktuğ.
You still don't listen to our Bey.
If he didn't hit you, that's because he
wanted you to be strong.
It's time to be strong and be worthy
of Osman Bey.
Come on.
Welcome, Priest.
Just sit and let's talk.
You don't need to be kind. You know
I'm not here willingly.
You made me come back here.
Not me.
This.
We both know that...
you're here for this.
As it's bringing you here, it's something
important...
tell me, what's that?
It's a heirloom.
It belongs to my grandfather.
We have it for years.
I want to give it to next
generations if you let me.
You hide it from your friend Rogatus...
it must be really valuable.
It is!
It is.
How do you know that?
Rogatus --
He was here.
When I told him what brought you
here is an heirloom...
he was surprised.
He was curious.
I understand that...
he doesn't know about that heirloom.
He doesn't.
It's not that I don't trust him.
It's an heirloom. It's normal that
he doesn't know.
He knows now.
Do you still trust Rogatus?
I always trust him, Osman Bey.
This trust will harm you, Priest.
Be careful.
Rogatus only wants to be stronger.
You call him your friend...
however, he uses you.
You think this heirloom
doesn't interest him...
I've seen his face.
If he knows that this heirloom...
will make him stronger...
then he will go after it.
- You're wrong, Osman Bey.
- Then you will meet face to face.
However, this heirloom won't be with you.
Let's see whether he will
choose you or this.
Why are we doing this?
I want to know your real intention.
What do you want from me, Osman Bey?
I want you to see what I saw, Priest.
In Bithynia, you and your heirloom...
isn't safe.
What if you're wrong?
What if Rogatus is loyal?
What if he treats me well?
Then I will set you free.
I will give your heirloom to you.
Okay.
I accept.
How do we meet Rogatus?
We shouldn't attract Rogatus' attention.
Osman Bey, send me back to church.
Rogatus will contact me.
What are you thinking, Priest?
Osman Bey...
I'm grateful that you're here.
Bithynia is small. The news spread.
You must have heard that...
Bey of Kayı, Osman has the Priest Gregor.
We heard that bad news.
You couldn't protect a Priest.
Osman aims to disrupt the...
unity of Christians.
As much as I know, Priest Gregor was
doing the same, Rogatus.
He was disrupting the unity of Christians
by going against the Emperor.
I just wanted to save my friend's life...
it's not about Osman, right Kosses?
If Osman continues to keeping Gregor...
he can have a say on
the Christian community.
That's why we should leave
the conflict among us and...
be together.
It's the only way we can make
Osman give Gregor back to us.
Do you want to tell us how, Rogatus?
Well, my dear friend...
we will stop everything they will
make benefit from.
For example...
the Turkmen employees
working in their mines...
my employees were teaching them
the key points of this job but...
I dismissed those vain people
because they didn't deserve...
to know this information.
My dear friend, Manuel, the
governor of İznik...
he broke the agreements with tradesmen
in Söğüt.
Right?
I assure you that Osman, the
Bey of Kayı...
is dreaming...
to be Süleyman Shah, son of the devil.
That's why my dear friend, Manuel, the
governor of İznik...
won't buy any Kayı rug.
We are breaking the agreement.
We won't buy any Kayı rug.
I want you to do the same thing.
Trade.
Trade...
is like a river...
when the river gets dry...
people around it...
start fighting.
Rogatus...
it's a well-thought idea.
I agree with Nikola.
Let's be together.
-You know the bey's order, Saltuk.
-I do, brother.
We'll leave them so that Gregor
can talk to the old man.
-But I don't understand why.
-Beys have secrets.
Come on.
You surprised me.
Why did you--
-We'll run away from the tribe. Help us.
-How can I help?
It's impossible. Osman Bey must've
taken every measure.
I planned everything. Just be at the
entrance of the tribe at the dawn.
You'll wait for us with two horses.
We'll go to the forest.
-Tell Rogatus to meet us there.
-It'll be difficult but alright.
I'll do it.
Well done, ladies.
-Thank Allah you've done it.
-Thank you, Mother Selcan.
Welcome, it's just time.
The carpets are ready.
They are waiting to be loaded.
But the carts?
Carts aren't coming. The agreement
is canceled. We aren't buying.
Wait there.
What does that mean?
I don't know. I'm tasked to inform.
What's this.
What is he saying, son?
They've broken the agreement.
They aren't buying.
-What will we do now?
-I don't know, mother. I don't know.
We need to inform Osman Bey.
If you allow me.
Cornelia, I didn't expect to have
so much fun here.
Your brother will be mad to hear
that we came here.
I can't help it. This tribe takes
you into itself.
What does changing minds at the
delivery date means?
There is something behind this.
What'll happen to all the carpets?
Is İznik the only place to sell our
carpets to?
Don't worry, ladies. Osman Bey
will find a way.
-Inshallah.
-Get to your work.
-Welcome, Mari.
-Welcome, my child.
Thank you.
This is my helper, Cornelia.
I wanted to introduce her to you.
She was curious about the
process.
Welcome, my child.
Carpets. Where are they going to?
It was supposed to be İznik but
we just received a messenger.
-They changed their mind.
-Why?
We don't know. The messenger
didn't say anything.
We'll find out when Osman Bey returns.
I'm sorry.
I came here to watch
the weaving of the carpets.
Come on, then.
Let's show you.
See how your carpets
are made.
Come.
-Good day.
-Welcome, my bey.
Thank you. Thank you.
-Good day.
-Welcome, my bey.
Thank you.
Have a good working day.
-Welcome, my bey.
-Welcome.
-How is your trade?
-Thank God it's good, my bad.
-Come.
-May Allah bless you.
-Good day.
-Thank you, my bey. Welcome.
Thank you.
Are you making enough?
Yes, my bey. Thank God.
-How is your trade.
-We work day and night for the orders.
It seems like we'll be very happy
after the sales.
-Inshallah, inshallah. May it prosper.
-Thank you, my bey.
-Göktuğ.
-My bey.
As you said, they are whispering.
They must be after something.
-Now, take Gregor back to the tribe.
-As you order, my bey.
-What is this, Baran?
-My bey, they are from Dudullu Tribe.
Sheik Edebali sent them...
to work in Rogatus' mines.
We'll find out now.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Now, tell me.
what is this?
We were working in the silver mines
of the lord of Bilecik.
He said ''Such an important job...
can't be done by such worthless people''
and he kicked us out.
You know the reason.
-Osman Bey.
-Brother.
It's not good, Osman Bey.
-What is it, brother?
-The carpet deal we made with İznik...
the deals we made with the merchants in
Söğüt, they are all canceled.
They are kicking the workers out.
They are canceling the deals.
Their intentions are obvious, brother.
They can't draw their swords but
they try to stop our trade.
It's getting harder, Osman Bey.
We don't like easy, brother.
They try to subjugate us by
doing this.
They think that we'll bow down.
But we bow down before nothing
but Allah.
Now, inform the tribe.
-I want the beys in my tribe.
-Alright, my bey.
Come on.
-Farewell, Bala Hatun.
-Until next time, Mari.
The carpets seem important to them.
They are very sad.
Yes, we'll take them out of
this despair, Cornelia.
Thanks to us, they'll sell
their carpets.
-Will your brother accept this?
-He has to.
If we buy the carpets, they'll believe
in our sincerity.
I don't want to miss the fun, Cornelia.
We'll have much more fun in this tribe.
Turgut Bey, you are freed.
I am, thank Allah.
And we'll punish the ones who
chained me.
I hope you won't fail again.
Why did you help me?
I owed you, Turgut Bey.
Did you forget? You saved me from that
snake.
And by helping you, I honored my debt.
Be careful, Turgut Bey.
I don't have a reason to save you now.
Come on.
Come, my child.
Do you really think she'll buy
the carpets?
I don't know but...
there is something off with
that woman.
I don't feel like she is sincere
with her words.
-It's like she's planning something.
-Time will show.
But if they buy the carpets, they'll
save us from trouble.
Look at these lords. We are happy
that Mari might buy the carpets now.
What will we do now.
Osman Bey will find a way. That's why
he's gathering the beys.
Malhun Hatun is right.
Osman Bey against the whole lords.
He'll unite with his beys
and find a way.
Inshallah. Inshallah.
What should be done to the enemy
who isn't keeping his word, Bala?
One who doesn't keep his word should
be punished regardless of the friendship.
So will we.
Trade isn't only flowing from the east
to the west.
Their caravans move around Turkmen tribes.
We'll find out when will
they pass from where...
so that we can punish them.
My bey.
They are taking their sea caravans from
the narrow strait behind my tribe.
My father Umur Bey never
attacked them.
It's for Osman Bey now.
I heard that they are taking
their spice caravans...
near Yılanlık.
They are protected well,
but not enough.
Tell me then, Turgut Bey.
How many alps can you gather?
All the tribesmen who can wield
a sword is an all of mine.
Just say the word, Osman Bey.
Then, tell your alps.
Osman Bey orders.
We'll know about their routes.
Not a single heathen caravan will
enter Bhytinia.
They won't leave Bhytinia.
-As you order, my bey.
This war is in between the heathens
and the Muslims.
Their real goal is to
gather under the cross...
and banish us
from these alnds.
We will gather under the light
of the crescent and stand against them.
Their unity is until they
turn their backs against each other.
But our unity has always been
back to back.
-Allah is with us.
Allah is with the believers, my bey.
-May you be victorious.
-Inshallah.
Inshallah.
If you allow me, my bey.
Osman Bey.
Bilecik Castle.
The news is good, Theodor.
Our friend seems to be succesful.
Tomorrow, Gregor will come here.
He'll be with a valuable relic.
You go to the caravan tomorrow.
I'll get the priest.
You took care of my tribe
in my absence.
Thank you.
Did we say all these things for nothing?
It's our duty to tend the wounds
of our brothers.
Then tell me this.
If you knew that Priest Gregor
wouldn't return...
would you still exchange him
with me?
Even the most precious of the heathens...
is not as valuable as you for me.
We wouldn't leave you behind, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
Turgut Bey's Tribe
It seems that Osman Bey wants
to lead the Turkmens.
Firstly, he should know of us.
Fate will show who will be the head.
Allah decides in the end, right?
We'll do what Osman Bey couldn't.
Tell me what you heard.
My bey, these catolonians
live for gold.
They don't have a home.
They camp in the woods.
Sometimes, they raid caravans.
They worship gold.
So, they raid caravans?
Prepare your alps, Kutan. We'll bury
Anselmo with the gold he raided.
My bey, I heard what happened.
The lords know that they can't beat us.
Now, they are targeting our trade.
Our people will have hard times.
Don't worry, my bey.
Don't think about that.
We'll support the people until
you take care of things.
We'll find a way.
Thank you, Malhun. You always
ease my burden.
You are giving me strenght.
Saltuk!
The priest escaped the church, my bey.
You are coming to your death
with your own feet, Gregor!
You are making my job easier!
- Welcome, Gregor.
- Thank God we reunited.
- We shall leave.
What are they doing here?
Let's go.
Do you think they will manage, sir?
I wouldn't be here if I didn't believe
that he'd come.
Gregor, here.
Wait.
We must be sure it's not a trap.
Gregor!
My dear friend Gregor.
I am very, very happy to see you again.
I am too, Lord Rogatus.
The thing that makes you come back...
That relic...
What?
Why did you come back?
What is the precious thing you
forgot in Osman's hand?
Osman must have tricked you.
This was just a little scar.
What is that precious thing that
you hide under your skin?
Stop lying to me!
- Where it is?
- I don't know!
- Let him go!
- I won't ask again!
I don't know!
Priest Gregor!
Do you see what I meant?
Neither Rogatus nor anyone else
cares about your life.
-Osman Bey is right, Gregor.
-Rogatus!
Don't!
Lower your dagger.
You aren't safe here.
You can't leave here.
Now...
Leave the priest.
You were the only one I trusted!
God damn it!
Father Gregor.
We are facing both Rogatus
and Kosses.
We'll go as the old ways, Diego.
Anselmo needs power.
Power needs gold.
If we move right now,
we'll reach the point by the sun fall.
And set the ambush.
What are we waiting for, Diego?
Tell the men to prepare.
Come on! Get up!
Come on!
I still can't understand!
He was my friend...
I'm embarrassed against you.
I didn't listen to you.
A proverb says...
''A calamity is better than a
thousand advises.''
Even if I had told you a thousand times,
you wouldn't get it before seeing it.
But you now understand that only safe
place in Bhytinia is...
my side.
-I understand it, Osman Bey.
Even though the truth slapped
me on my face, I do.
I want to meet the Christian folk
in Söğüt.
If you allow me, I want to let them
now that I'm with them now.
Then, let's go to Söğüt.
Bilecik Castle
That vile priest united with
Osman and tried to test me!
This is unbelievable!
My friend Gregor,
if friendships are in the past...
your life lost its value.
Whatever he is hiding,
we'll find out.
I have one more bad news.
While you were busy with Gregor...
they attacked the mine!
The mine! Osman!
Osman!
Priest Gregor will live
with us here now.
My sheik.
Priest Gregor.
Sheik Edebali, the candle that
enlightens our paths...
the light of the Kayı.
Welcome, priest.
We are delighted by your
arrivel...
as much as the non-Muslims.
I'm grateful for your kindness,
Sheik Edebali.
We are happy to see you.
We would like you to visit
our lodge soon.
-Priest Gregor.
-Of course. So do I, Sheik Edebali.
My sheik.
Come, Priest Gregor.
Good job, Diego.
I hope they are loaded as you said.
Don't doubt that, Leader Anselmo.
Attack!
If you want to survive,
give us your goods!
Give them!
Come on!
That was easy.
Pleasing, isn't it?
Haven't you heard it?
If you want to survive,
give us your goods!
Alps!
It's time for revenge, Anselmo!
So be it, Turgut.
Let's see if you are as brave when
I'm not tied up.
Anselmo is always brave.
But you aren't a good swordsman
even when you are free.
Don't speak, come at me!
Come at me!
I told you!
I will choke you on your gold!
Go to hell!
-They are retreating!
-Anselmo!
Kutan, send the wounded to the tribe.
We'll take their corpses
to Osman Bey.
As you order, my bey.
Wouldn't we be impressed...
if we heard how the Christ
begged God...
for unity among us...
and unity with God?
Now, we hear this beseeching
with our eyes from the holy book.
The separation among our people,
rivalry...
and the tendency for selfishness
is strong but...
we Christians should be the agents
of unity.
Priest Gregor!
Hang on!
Master Gregor!
My unlucky master!
With the name of Allah.
-Osman Bey.
-Brother.
My sheik.
My bey, Baysungur is here.
We have a word from our scouts.
We know the route of Rogatus' caravan.
Be quick! We must reach Bilecik Castle
at once!
Guards! Keep your eyes open!
Alps! They'll be here soon.
Now is the time for a clash!
Now is the time for a slaughter!
You'll take all the goods.
Not a single man will survive.
As you order, my bey.
Come on!
Take defensive formation!
Protect the caravan!
God is with us!
Allahu Akbar!
Theodor! If God is with you...
why are you running away like a
jackal running from a lion?
Face me, then!
Come on!
Come on! Come on, brothers!
My shoulder was cut so many
times that I feel nothing now.
When I behead you, you will feel it.
If you don't want me to kill you,
tell me everything.
The other caravans of your master.
Their routes.
Their loads too.
You will tell me everything.
How many soldiers are waiting
at Bilecik Castle?
How many soldiers does Rogatus have
in his villages?
Tell me everything!
Never.
So, your life isn't precious?
I won't make it easier for you, Osman Bey.
Finally, Heaven.
I doubt that's where you are heading.
The only place you will go is hell!
My bey, you didn't leave
anyone alive.
We have the goods, my bey.
They thought that we would give up
after they strike our trade!
But they couldn't see the truth
because of the light of our swords!
Now, we'll show them the truth!
Long live Osman Bey!
Take his head.
We are going to the lords.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com